Guide to the David Trinidad Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS.106
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2002. Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence 1970-2002
    - Kralick, John E. DT, miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 101)
    - Kralick, John E. DT, miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 102)
    - Kralick, John E. DT (Box 2002.02, Folder 103)
    - Kralick, John E. DT, poems 1970s, ca. 1970 (Box 2002.02, Folder 104)
    - Kraus, Chris, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 105)
    - Krukowski, Damon, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 106)
    - Kyger, Joanne, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 107)
    - La Bombard, Joan, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 108)
    - Lally, Michael, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 109)
    - Larkin, Joan, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 110)
    - Lassell, Michael, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 111)
    - Laux, Dorianne, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 112)
    - Leddy, Michael, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 113)
    - Lederer, Katherine, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 114)
    - Lehman, David, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 115)
    - Luezzi, Tony, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 116)
    - Levenson, Robin, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 117)
    - Liu, Timothy, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 118)
    - Lyons, Kimberly, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 119)
    - McCormack, Derek, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 120)
    - Macdonald, Laura, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 121)
    - McCain, Gillian, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 122)
    - Martin, Douglas, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 123)
    - Merla, Patrick, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 124)
    - Moody, Rick, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 125)
    - Moore, Thurston, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 126)
    - Mosher, Daniel, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 127)
    - Muldoon, Paul, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 128)
    - Muske-Dukes, Carol, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 129)
    - Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 130)
    - Nauen, Elinor, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 131)
    - Newman, Leslea, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 132)
    - Neilsen, David, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 133)
    - Nolan, Pat, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 134)
    - Northup, Harry, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 135)
    - Notley, Alice, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 136)
    - Ossip, Kathy, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 137)
    - Ostriker, Alicia, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 138)
    - Owen, Maureen, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 139)
    - Norton, Rosanna, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 140)
    - Packer, Eve, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 141)
    - Padgett, Ron, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 142)
    - Parker, Alan Michael, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 143)
    - Peabody, Richard, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 144)
    - Peacock, Molly, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 145)
    - Pearlberg, Gerry Gomez, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 146)
    - Peery, Janet, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 147)
    - Phillips, Carl, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 148)
    - Polito, Robert, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 149)
    - Powell, Doug, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 150)
    - Pugsley, Alex, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 151)
    - Pullinger, Kate, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 152)
    - Rackin, Ethel, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 153)
    - Revell, Donald, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 154)
    - Rice, Rich, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 155)
    - Rosenstock, Helen, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 156)
    - Sala, Jerome, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 157)
    - Scalera, Holly, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 158)
    - Scates, Maxine, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 159)
    - Scates, Maxine Uprooting manuscript, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 160)
    - Scates, Maxine. "On the Poetry of Ann Stanford, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 161)
    - Schimel, Lawrence, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 162)
    - Scholder, Amy, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 163)
    - Seaton, Maureen, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 164)
    - Selman, Robyn, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 165)
    - Shalforoosh, Soroya, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 166)
    - Shalforoosh, Soroya, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 167)
    - Sharma, Pargeeta, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 168)
    - Sheck, Laurie, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 169)
    - Shepherd, Reginald, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 170)
    - Sick, Robert, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 171)
    - Silverberg, Ira, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 172)
    - Skelley, Jack, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 173)
    - Smith, Joan Jobe, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 174)
    - Sullivan, Billy, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 175)
    - Taylor, Marvin, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 176)
    - Teasley, Lisa, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 177)
    - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 178)
    - Timmons, Susie, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 179)
    - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 180)
    - Ulin, David L., undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 181)
    - Upshaw, Reagan, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 182)
    - Wakoski, Diane, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 183)
    - Waldman, Anne, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 184)
    - Warsh, Lewis, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 185)
    - Wieser, Karen, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 186)
    - Weissman, Benjamin, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 187)
    - Welt, Bernard, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 188)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 189)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 190)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 191)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 192)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 193)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 194)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 195)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 196)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 197)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 198)
    - Wheeler, Susan. Handmade postcards to DT, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 199)
    - Wheeler, Susan. "In the Feckless Light: Poems" (B.A. Thesis), undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 200)
    - Wheeler, Susan. "Re: Chapbook 4" inscribed to DT, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 201)
    - Wheeler, Susan "Source Codes" manuscript with notes to DT, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 202)
    - Wheeler, Susan. "Start Up" inscribed to DT, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 203)
    - Wigers, Michael, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 204)
    - Winch, Terence, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 205)
    - Winkfield, Trevor, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 206)
    - Wojahn, David, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 207)
    - Wolverton, Terry, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 208)
    - Wormser, Baron, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 209)
    - Yablonsky, Linda, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 210)
    - Yang, Naomi, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 211)
    - Zucker, Rachel, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 212)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence from Family
    - Trinidad, Rubert [father], undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 1)
    - Trinidad, Ross [brother], undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 2)
    - Trinidad, Linda [sister; married name: Jackson], undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 3)
    - Jackson Family, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 4)
    - Fin, Louise [aunt], undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 5)
    - Relatives, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence Regarding Publications
    - Serpent's Tail, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Department of State, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 2)
    - Magazines/Journals (Box 2002.03, Folder 3)
    - Magazines/Journals, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 4)
    - Magazines/Journals, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 5)
    - Anthologies, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 6)
    - Anthologies, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 7)
    - Reference Books, undated (Box 2002.03, Folder 8)
    - Readings, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 9)
    - Readings, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 10)
    - Readings, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 11)
    - Fun Factory, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 12)
    - Ann Stanford Collected Poetry, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 13)
    - Ann Stanford Collected Poetry, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - High School Friends, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 1)
    - High School Friends, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 2)
    - High School Friends, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 3)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 4)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 5)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 6)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 7)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 8)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 9)
    - Students, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 10)
    - Judgings, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 11)
    - Fan Mail, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 12)
    - Fan Mail, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 13)
    - Fan Mail, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 14)
    - Fan Mail, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 7)
- Accretions 2002. Series II: Writing
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts
    - Plasticville manuscript, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 1)
    - Plasticville rejection letters, etc., undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 2)
    - Plasticville uncorrected galleys, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 3)
    - Plasticville Blurbs on, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 4)
    - Plasticville Production miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 5)
    - Plasticville Cover Flats, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 6)
    - Plasticville Cover Flats [design options], undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 7)
    - Plasticville Press Releases, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 8)
    - Plasticville Comp List, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 9)
    - Plasticville Mailing Lists, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 10)
    - Plasticville Mailing Lists, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 11)
    - Plasticville Mailing Lists, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 12)
    - Plasticville Mailing Lists, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 13)
    - Plasticville Soroya Follow-up Calls, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 14)
    - Plasticville Reviews, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 15)
    - Plasticville Reviews, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 16)
    - Plasticville, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 17)
    - Plasticville Reveiws, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 18)
    - Plasticville Times Bestseller List, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 19)
    - Plasticville D.A.P. Catalogue Spring-Summer 2000 (Box 2002.04, Folder 20)
    - Plasticville Tour Correspondence, undated (Box 2002.04, Folder 21)
  - Subseries B: Poetry Worksheets 1998-2001
    - For Joe Brainard, 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 1)
    - Aborted Worksheets, 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 2)
    - Pantoum, 1 May 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 3)
    - Ann Lauterbach Pink. 5 July 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 4)
    - Almost Thirty Years Later 18 Aug. 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 5)
    - Watching the Late Movie with My Mother. August 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 6)
    - The Late Show. August 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 7)
    - Slicker. 14 September 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 8)
    - Kid Stuff By Oscar Wilde. 4 Octover 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 9)
    - From the LIfe of Joe Brainard 5 November 1998 (Box 2002.04, Folder 10)
    - A Poet's Death 27 Jan. 1999- 12 March 1999 (Box 2002.04, Folder 11)
    - October 6, 1999. 9 October 1999. (Box 2002.04, Folder 12)
    - October 5, 1999. 9 October 1999 (Box 2002.04, Folder 13)
    - Candy Necklace. 7 June 2000 (Box 2002.04, Folder 14)
    - Joe Brainard Pink. 2 August 2000 (Box 2002.04, Folder 15)
    - Old Scores 10 August 2000 (Box 2002.04, Folder 16)
    - 9 Cigarettes. 30 August 2000 (Box 2002.04, Folder 17)
    - Ed. 11 Feb. 2000 (Box 2002.04, Folder 18)
    - Two Sonnets. 17 Nov. 2001 (Box 2002.04, Folder 19)
    - Collected Work, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 20)
    - Collected Work 10 August 1988-7 April 1992, 1988-1992 (Box 2002.05, Folder 21)
    - Collected Work 17 May 1992- 25 July 1997, 1992-1997 (Box 2002.05, Folder 22)
    - False Apocalypse., undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Poems., undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: Collaborations
    - Chain Chain Chain. 15 September 1999- 19 December 1999 version (Box 2002.05, Folder 1)
    - Chain Chain Chain. Final manuscript version, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 2)
    - Chain Chain Chain. Byron Book edition, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 3)
    - Chain Chain Chain. Author's reading copy, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 4)
  - Subseries F: Essays
    - Ann Sexton: An Actress in her own Autobiographical Play. MS and Background Material. June 2001. (Box 2002.05, Folder 1)
    - Tiffany Blue(s). MS and Background material. July 2000 (Box 2002.05, Folder 2)
    - Holding Her Own. MS and Correspondence. August 2000 (Box 2002.05, Folder 3)
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous Writing
    - Introductions by DT, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 1)
    - Reading Copies, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 3)
  - Subseries I: General Background and Source Material
    - A Poet's Death. Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 1)
    - Tim Dlugos, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 2)
    - Sylvia Plath File, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 3)
    - Psycho File, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 4)
    - Truman Capote File, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 5)
    - Natalie Wood File, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 6)
    - Patty Duke File, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 7)
    - Movies, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 8)
    - Songs, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 9)
    - "What a Way to Go!", undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 10)
    - KHJ Top 300 1966 (Box 2002.05, Folder 11)
    - Yardley, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 12)
    - Barbie Tearsheets, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 13)
    - Barbie Tearsheets, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 14)
    - Barbie Tearsheets, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 15)
    - Barbie Tearsheets, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 16)
    - Caollectables, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 17)
    - Toys, undated (Box 2002.05, Folder 18)
    - Magazine Clippings, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 19)
    - Magazine Clippings, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 20)
    - Various Articles, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 21)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 24)
    - Valley of the Dolls, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 25)
    - Valley of the Dolls, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 26)
  - Subseries J: Phoebe 2002
    - Background. All about Eve file, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 1)
    - Background. "Everything About Eve" by Sam Staggs., undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 2)
    - Gackground. Maureen Owen Epic Workshop, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 3)
    - Background. Section of Paradise Lost., undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 4)
    - Phoebe Style Sheet, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 5)
    - Phoebe 2002. 4 Feb. 2000 (Box 2002.06, Folder 6)
    - Phoebe 2002. 4 Feb. 2000 (Box 2002.06, Folder 7)
    - Phoebe 2002. 4 Feb. 2000 (Box 2002.06, Folder 8)
    - Phoebe 2002. 4 Feb. 2000 (Box 2002.06, Folder 9)
    - Phoebe 2002. Second Draft, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 10)
    - Phoebe 2002. Second Draft, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 11)
    - Phoebe 2002. New Master, Books 1-7, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 12)
    - Phoebe 2002. New Master, Books 8-11, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 13)
    - Phoebe 2002. New Master, Book 12, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 14)
    - Phoebe 2002. New Master, Book 13, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 15)
    - Phoebe 2002. New Master, Book 14, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 16)
    - Phoebe 2002. New Master, Book 15, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 17)
    - Phoebe 2002. Notes, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 18)
    - Phoebe 2002. Notes, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 19)
    - Phoebe 2002. Reading Drafts, notes, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 20)
  - Subseries K: Jackie Susann
    - Jackie Susann Archive Finding Aid, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 1)
    - Jackie Susann File, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 2)
    - Jackie Susann File, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 3)
    - Jackie Susann File, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 4)
    - Jackie Susann File, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 5)
    - Dogs, Dames, and Dolls. Background Material, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 6)
    - Dogs, Dames, and Dolls. Early Proofs. located in oversize box, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 7)
    - Dogs, Dames, and Dolls. Proofs., undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 8)
    - Jackie Susann Cover Story. Publisher's Weekly., 1968 (Box 2002.06, Folder 9)
    - My Life with Jackie. MS copy Part 1, undated (Box 2002.06, Folder 10)
    - My Life with Jackie. MS Copy Part 2, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 11)
    - Underneath the Pancake. Part I. MS Copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 12)
    - Underneath the Pancake. Part II. MS Copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 13)
    - Underneath the Pancake. Part III. MS copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 14)
    - Valley of the Dolls. Early MS copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 15)
    - Return to the Valley of the Dolls. MS Copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 16)
    - Return to the Valley of the Dolls. MS copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 17)
    - Lovely Me (play). MS copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 18)
    - Along Came Joe., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 19)
    - Watching the Clock, or Once Is Not Enough., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 20)
    - Where Eid Everybody Go? Corrected copy, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 21)
    - Ruth Berle Story., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 22)
    - Watching the Clock., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 23)
    - Who Killed Cock Robin?, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 28)
    - Theme from Valley of the Dolls Sheet Music. located in oversize box, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 29)
    - Valley of teh Dolls. Promotional Material. Located in oversize box., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 30)
  - Subseries L: Editorial Work
    - Ann Stanford Miscellaneous Poems., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 1)
    - The Skyrocked. MS from Ann Stanford Archive, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 2)
    - Dreaming. MS from Ann Stanford Archive, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 3)
    - Ann Stanford Selected Poetry. Reviews, Press, etc., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 4)
    - Ann Stanford Selected Poetry. Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 5)
    - Fun Factory. Original MS, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 6)
    - Fun Factory. MS, undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 7)
    - Fun Factory. Pre-publication, Misc., undated (Box 2002.07, Folder 8)
- Accretions 2002. Series IV
  - Subseries A: Reviews of Books, Interviews, Articles About
    - Interviews, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 4)
    - Internet Printouts, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 5)
    - Articles, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Articles and Books David Trinidad Mentioned In
    - Articles, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 3)
    - Articles, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 4)
    - Articles, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 5)
    - Academy of American Poets., undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 6)
  - Subseries E: Readings 1978-2002
    - 1998 (Box 2002.08, Folder 1)
    - 1999 (Box 2002.08, Folder 2)
    - 2000 (Box 2002.08, Folder 3)
    - 2001 (Box 2002.08, Folder 4)
    - 2002 (Box 2002.08, Folder 5)
  - Subseries F: Teaching 1990-2001
    - Photo. DT at desk, signed and inscribed by his students, 1990 (Box 2002.08, Folder 1)
    - Course Packet. Genre Writing., 2001 (Box 2002.08, Folder 2)
    - MFA Rsidency Guide. Antioch University, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 3)
    - MFA in Creative Writing Selected Readings. Antioch University, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Introductory Packets. Antioch University, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 5)
    - MFA in Creative Writing Selected Readings. Antioch University, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 6)
    - Poems for Class. Master Hnadout, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 7)
    - Poems for Class. Master copy, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 8)
    - Letters of Recommendation, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 9)
    - Student Questionaires, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 10)
    - Course Evaluations, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 11)
    - Antioch June 2001 Residency (Box 2002.08, Folder 12)
    - Antioch December 2001 Residency (Box 2002.08, Folder 13)
    - Antioch June 2002 Residency (Box 2002.08, Folder 14)
    - Antioch Project Period Summer/Fall 2001 (Box 2002.08, Folder 15)
    - Antioch Project Period, Winter/Spring 2002 (Box 2002.08, Folder 16)
    - Antioch Project Period, Winter/Spring 2002 (Box 2002.08, Folder 17)
    - Antioch Seminar Materials, undated (Box 2002.08, Folder 18)
    - AWp Conference, April 2001 (Box 2002.08, Folder 19)
    - Course Materials. Princeton. Fall 2000 (Box 2002.08, Folder 20)
    - Poetry Workshop Handbook. New School, Fall 1999. (Box 2002.09, Folder 21)
    - MFA Thesis. Amanda Lea Johnson. New School., 2001 (Box 2002.09, Folder 22)
    - New School, Spring 1999. Thesis Students. (Box 2002.09, Folder 23)
    - New School, Spring 2000. Thesis Students (Box 2002.09, Folder 24)
    - New School, Spring 2001. Thesis Students (Box 2002.09, Folder 25)
    - New School, Spring 2002. Thesis Students. (Box 2002.09, Folder 26)
    - Course Materials. New School, Poetry Workshop. Fall 1999 (Box 2002.09, Folder 27)
    - Course Materials. New School, Poetry Workshop, Fall 2000 (Box 2002.09, Folder 28)
    - Course Materials. New School, Poetry Workshop, Fall 2001 (Box 2002.09, Folder 29)
    - Poems for Workshops, undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 30)
    - Handout for First Class. Rutgers 300 Level, undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 31)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 300. Fall 1999 (Box 2002.09, Folder 32)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 300, Spring 1999 (Box 2002.09, Folder 33)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 400, Spring 1999 (Box 2002.09, Folder 34)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 400, Fall 2000. (Box 2002.09, Folder 35)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 300, Spring 2000 (Box 2002.09, Folder 36)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 400, Spring 2000. (Box 2002.09, Folder 37)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 300, Fall 2001. (Box 2002.09, Folder 38)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 300, Spring 2001. (Box 2002.09, Folder 39)
    - Course Materials. Rutgers, English 400, Spring 2001. (Box 2002.09, Folder 40)
    - Student Contests. Rutgers., 1999 (Box 2002.09, Folder 41)
    - Student Contests. Rutgers. Spring 2000. (Box 2002.09, Folder 42)
    - Student Contests. Rutgers. Spring 2001. (Box 2002.09, Folder 43)
    - Writers at Rutgers, Reading Series., undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 44)
    - Writers at Rutgers. 1996 Posters. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.09, Folder 45)
    - Writers at Rutgers. 1997 Posters. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.09, Folder 46)
    - Writers at Rutgers. 1998 Posters. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.09, Folder 47)
    - Writers at Rutgers. 1999 Posters. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.09, Folder 48)
    - Writers at Rutgers. 2000 Posters. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.09, Folder 49)
    - Writers at Rutgers. 2001 Posters. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.09, Folder 50)
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous
    - Publications List, undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 1)
    - Memberships/Contributions., undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 2)
    - Guggenheim Fellowship Application, undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 3)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 4)
    - Resume, original, undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 5)
    - Sherwood Press. Amy Gerstler, "Christy's Alpine Inn", undated (Box 2002.09, Folder 6)
  - Subseries H: Notebooks 1984-2002
    - Notebook. September 1998. (Box 2002.09, Folder 1)
    - Notebook. June 30, 1999 (Box 2002.09, Folder 2)
    - Notebook. June 2000. (Box 2002.09, Folder 3)
    - Notebook. June 200-June 2001, 200-2001 (Box 2002.09, Folder 4)